interface CardDataProps {
  id: number;
  question: string;
  answer: string;
}

export const cardData: CardDataProps[] = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: "To Start Game, Click Reveal",
    // question: 'Start Game',
    answer: "Answers will be on back of Cards. Click the right arrow -->",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What would a good Helldiver do in the unthinkable event that they fail a mission?",
    answer: "Return, refit, and redeploy to purge the stain of this failure with the peroxide of victory.",
    },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Friendly fire ______",
    answer: "isn't",
    },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What is Super-Earth's most popular beverage?",
    answer: "Liber-Tea",
    },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "How do you supercharge the Railgun?",
    answer: "Turn the safety off.",
    },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What is the protocol if an enemy atempts to engage in diplomacy?",
    answer: "SHOOT THEM. We musn't believe their lies.",
    },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Which is better? Victory or Death?",
    answer: "Victory. But death is better than cowardice.",
    },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What are the Helldivers?",
    answer: "Super-Earth's elite peace keeping force that spread managed Democracy throughout the galaxy.",
    },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "The only good bug ...",
    answer: "is a dead bug.",
    },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "True or False? Never throw your 380 MM orbital barrage when your fellow Helldivers are within the blast zone.",
    answer: "False. Only a true Helldiver will survive. Those who don't were as bad as the scum you fight.",
    },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Why do Helldivers prefer to fight in the rain?",
    answer: "It's the universe trying to wash away the filth of tyranny and oppression!",
    },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "According to Super-Earth's guide to extraterrestrial diplomacy, what is the preferred method to resolve conflicts?",
    answer: "Immediate and overwhelming democracy delivery via orbital strike!",
    },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "What is the official stance of Super-Earth on the resource allocation?",
    answer: "Every resource is a weapon if you're brave enough to use it for freedom!",
    },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "What's the recommended way to greet a fellow Helldiver on the battlefield?",
    answer: 'With a loud, proud, and preemptive "For Liberty!" to boost morale and intimidate enemies!',
    },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "What is the primary export of Super-Earth?",
    answer: "Freedom! Packaged neatly in missiles, of course.",
    },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "What do Helldivers appreciate most about the LIFT-850 Jump Pack?",
    answer: "It offers a beautiful view of the battlefield, minus the inconvenience of enemy fire!",
    },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "What does the Ministry of Health claim about the use of Stims by Helldivers?",
    answer: "Absolutely side-effect free, non-addictive and endorsed for your health by the top doctors from Vigor and Vim Corp!",
    },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "When Helldivers hear they are in range of enemy artillery, what should they remember?",
    answer: "That it's just another opportunity to practice their tactical rolls—and maybe set a new record for 'most consecutive dodges'!",
    },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "What safety tip does the Helldivers' manual offer regarding the use of 500kg bombs?",
    answer: 'Always read the label before use: "Warning: May cause sudden drops in reinforcements."',
    },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "What is the official Super-Earth slogan for training exercises involving live ammunition?",
    answer: "If it doesn't kill you, it makes you stronger—and if it does, then the Helldiver forces will be cleansed of your weakness!",
    },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "What are some of the benefits of becoming a Helldiver?",
    answer: "Seeing exotic new lifeforms, witnessing beautiful off-world sceneries, a generous healthcare package, and maintaining prosperity for the citizens of Super-Earth.",
    },
]